wishstargames.com 2013-12-09

# Privacy Policy | Wish Star Games

This Privacy Policy provides information about Wishstargames.com’s collection and use of certain information, including Personal identifiable Information, about its users obtained by Wishstargames.com via this Site only. “Personal Identifiable Information” is specific information about users that enables Wishstargames.com to identify you, such as your name, e-mail address and/or home address. BEFORE UTILIZING THIS SITE, BROWSING THIS SITE, SUBMITTING ANY INFORMATION VIA THIS SITE AND/OR USING ANY SERVICES AVAILABLE THROUGH THIS SITE, PLEASE READ ALL OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE Wishstargames.com TERMS and CONDITIONS (“AGREEMENT”) CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING ANY AREAS OF THIS SITE, USERS (“USERS” OR “YOU”) AGREE TO BE LEGALLY BOUND AND TO ABIDE BY THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THE AGREEMENT AND THIS PRIVACY POLICY. We are committed to working to protect the privacy and security of the information we may gather about you, and we will endeavor to use and share that information carefully and sensibly.

**A SPECIAL NOTE ABOUT CHILDREN**  
This Site is not designed or intended for use by children under 13 years of age. Although children’s products and/or services are referenced on this Site, this site is intended for use by adults. If you are under 18 years of age, you should use this Site only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. Children under 13 years of age may not submit any Personally Identifiable Information to us. If we discover that we have inadvertently gathered any such information from a child under 13 years of age, we will take appropriate steps to delete it.

**HOW INFORMATION IS COLLECTED**  
The information we learn from Users helps us personalize and continually improve this Site. Below are the general types of information we gather. Information You Give Us In general, you may visit this Site without providing any Personally Identifiable Information about yourself, except as otherwise stated, unless you choose to provide such information. For example, you are not required to but you may choose to provide us with Personally Identifiable Information if you submit questions or comments, answer or respond to surveys or reviews, save your products or research, utilize certain on-line services or participate in certain online activities. Information Gathered Automatically We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use “cookies” to obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses this Site. Briefly, “cookies” are small files that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive or your Web browser memory to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide convenience and other features to you. Examples of the information we collect and analyze in this manner include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; cookie number; your activities on our Site and related services, including the products and/or services you view or search for, as well as the URL you come from and go to next (whether this URL is on our site or not); and products and/or research you have chosen to save. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although, in that case, you may not be able to use certain features or services on the Site.

**HOW INFORMATION IS USED**  
Information that is collected about Users via this Site, including Personally Identifiable Information, is generally used for such purposes as customizing the Site; improving our services; providing you with the features or services requested; and communicating with you if you have authorized such communication. From time to time, Wishstargames.com may contact you to request feedback on your experience using the Site or to offer special savings or promotions. Aggregate information about Users may be used to perform certain analysis on Users of the Site.

**HOW INFORMATION IS SHARED**  
In an effort to serve you better and improve your online experiences, we may share information, including Personally Identifiable Information, in a responsible manner as described below. Agents and Vendors From time to time, we employ other companies and individuals to perform various functions on our behalf. Examples include sending postal mail and e-mail, analyzing user data and providing other data and services. In such instances, these companies and individuals may have access to information about you that is needed to perform their functions. Business Transactions As we continue to develop our business, we may participate in corporate transactions, such as mergers and acquisitions, and it is possible that another company may acquire Wishstargames.com or its business assets in the future. In such cases, User information may be shared with the acquirer and/or other parties involved in those transactions. Third Parties Except as otherwise provided, individual Personally Identifiable Information is not sold to third parties. Information in the aggregate, that does not identify any specific person, may, however, be sold to third parties. Protection of Wishstargames.com and Others Information about you may be released to third parties, to protect against or investigate fraud or other potentially harmful or illegal activities, if required by law and/or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against claims. With Your Consent Other than as described above, with your consent at the time you submit information to us, we may also share this information with additional third parties. Once we share information with your consent with a third party, the use and protection of that information by the third party will be subject to the privacy policies of that party. You may opt-out of such sharing of your information by declining to provide it or by sending a subsequent opt-out request to paul.blogpost [at] gmail [dot] com; however, opting-out may limit our ability to provide you with a specific service or feature.

**HOW INFORMATION IS PROTECTED**  
The safeguarding of Personally Identifiable Information is important to Wishstargames.com. To help prevent unauthorized access and maintain data accuracy we will employ reasonable and current Internet security methods and technologies. The Personally Identifiable Information you provide to us is stored in an environment that is designed to be secure. We use a secure server hosting location, firewall protection, controlled access and encryption technology to protect Personally Identifiable Information. While no system is completely foolproof, we take security very seriously, and our security measures are designed to protect information in a responsible manner.

**YOUR CHOICES**  
As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide Personally Identifiable Information, although not providing such information might prevent us from personalizing our site for you or prevent you from taking advantage of certain useful features. You may request Personally Identifiable Information to be deleted from certain files at any time by contacting paul.blogpost [at] gmail [dot] com. We will, however, retain information you have requested us to delete in some circumstances, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Agreement. Furthermore, such information is never completely removed from all of our databases due to technical and legal constraints, including stored “back up” systems.

**E-MAIL POLICIES**  
From time to time, Wishstargames.com may send newsletters and other e-mail to Users who have agreed to be contacted by Wishstargames.com. You can always choose not to receive certain types of e-mail from Wishstargames.com. Each of our e-mail messages contains instructions on how you may unsubscribe from receiving such e-mails.

**PRIVACY QUESTIONS**  
If you have any questions or concerns about privacy at Wishstargames.com, please contact us at the addresses listed below. We will do our best try to answer your questions or otherwise resolve the matter to your satisfaction.

**REVISIONS**  
Wishstargames.com reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on this Site. The amended terms shall be effective from and after the date that they are posted on the Site.

**HOW TO CONTACT US**

Should you have any questions, concerns or comments please e-mail us at wishstargames [at] gmail [dot] com
